{
    "id": "8c257a145fde42e5a7340f4c5fa68621",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The car is running more smoothly ………………… .. it had a service.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "69a7dab53cb7472fb5dfce6de16a8910"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… Mike is married, he is much more responsible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Now that",
                "Such that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d1065b23a231422ab5e70ea5a6f04586"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t settled the question of ………………… I’ll go back home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c15c0f0239944f190e16d644b584c73"
        },
        {
            "question": "They held the meeting on a holiday ………………….. everyone would be free to attend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in order for",
                "in order that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f3be2e29f51946999e8d55139a8edc42"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. she hadn’t prepared for the presentation, she did a commendable job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4223bd521eba4e45bfa18ce45fa3fce6"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. I told you earlier, the meeting has been postponed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2438a9507d014685abb6bc5ca5006e5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "My doctor told me to avoid fatty foods …………………… .. burgers and cheese.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "such as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bccbe0e2571e4c26a2871742e6d42cc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………… a loud noise ………………….. to wake everybody in the whole neighborhood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such ....as...",
                "so...that.."
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5aba2c44af574a7395de8a8750232d91"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… much he eats, he never gets fat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Whatever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "86103ef17a744741acc9d6b41ba5d3f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He accepted the challenge ……………………… he had been waiting for it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "as though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7490685ba0ec494cbfd7f76a3bc6f6a2"
        }
    ]
}